(Bernadette:)You one of those people?
(Penny:)No. No, no, no.
I-I think the cookie thing.
(Amy:)Action.
(Sheldon:)Welcome back.
(Sheldon:)Our guest today
is a returning fan favorite.
(Sheldon:)He puts the reading
in your rainbow,
(Sheldon:)the Geordi in your La Forge,
(Sheldon:)and the Kunta in your Kinte,
(Sheldon:)Mr. LeVar Burton.
(LeVar Burton:)Thank you, Sheldon.
Now, remember our deal...
(Sheldon:)You do this, I delete
your contact information.
(Penny:)While...
(Sheldon:)While you watch me do it.
(LeVar:)Great. Happy to be back.
(Sheldon:)Well, since you're here,
(Sheldon:)I'd like to get your
opinion on something.
In honor of Black
History Month,
(Sheldon:)I portrayed George
Washington Carver
(Sheldon:)in a loving tribute that my
roommate called "wildly racist."
(Sheldon:)What do you think?
SHELDON:
Hi. My name is George.
Oh, hell, no!